《邊橋謎案》前情提要
Previously on The Bridge...
我的天吶
Holy shit.
鮑勃  我一直對她有非分之想
Bob, I've been thinking about her in a special way.
下車吧
Here we go.
你干什么  戴維
What are you doing, David?
退后  退后
Get back! Go back!
他媽的到底搞什么
Wwhat the hell's going on?
炸彈已經激活  讓狙擊手待命
Bomb's live. Have your sniper stand down.
他已經激活了炸藥
He's activated the dead man's switch.
只要你告訴兒子的下落  你想干什么都行
Do whateve you have to do and tell me where my son is!
拿出你的槍
Take out your gun.
很好  現在瞄準他
Good. Now point it at him.
我跟你不一樣
I'm not like you.
你這樣救不了任何人
You're not saving anyone.
丹尼爾
Daniel.
我也許知道他在哪
I think I know where he is.
格斯  馬克  不要開槍
Gus! Marco! Don't shoot.
-桑婭  -我找到格斯了
- Sonya. - I found Gus.
-她在說謊  -他還活著嗎
- She's lying. - Did you find him alive?
不
No.
上帝保佑你  史蒂文
Blessings, Steven.
-雞不錯啊  -是啊  她不肯下蛋
- Nice chicken. - Yeah, well, she won' lay,
我估計她吃了不少咖啡渣
and I'm... I'm thinking maybe she got into some coffee grounds.
你覺得她像吃過嗎
She seem caffeinated to you?
-她像只雞  -對啊
- Seems like a chicken. - Yeah.
什么風把你吹來了
What brings you here?
我得到了啟示
I've had revelation.
-說吧  -伊娃
- Tell it. - Eva.
我想娶她做我妻子
I want to make her my wife.
這有些突然
That's kind of sudden.
我打算向她求婚  如果她同意了
I'm gonna ask for her hand, and, uh, if she says yes,
那就由你來主持婚禮
then, uh, you're gonna perform the ceremony.
我深感榮幸  哥們  但是伊娃走了
I'm honored, brother. But Eva's gone.
她沒走
She can't be.
她走了
She is.
-什么時候的事  -一周前
- When? - Week.
她說她想靜一靜
Said she wanted off the path.
你該告訴我這事的
You could've told me about this.
我要找到她
I'm gonna find her.
運氣不好啊
是啊
你去哪
科洛涅阿斯
我能帶你去
不用了  謝謝
我去搭巴士
那好吧  請載我一程吧
車架彎曲  機體毀壞
The frame's bent, engine block's demolished.
這就是所謂的全損
This here's what we call a total loss.
我要你修好它
Well, I need it fixed.
我不知道從何下手
I wouldn't know where to start.
花多少錢我都認
I'll pay whatever it costs.
花更少的錢  你就能買到一輛新烈馬
You could buy a new Bronco for less.
我不想要新...
I don't want a new...!
我不想要新的烈馬  我就想要這輛
I don't want a new Bronco. I want this one.
女士  我耳朵很靈
Lady, I-I got good hearing.
這個技工簡直太沒用了
This mechanic' useless.
多年來我一直都在請他修車
Well, I've been using him for years.
他固執的要命
Well, he's very stubborn.
沒錯
He is.
他讓我扔了它
He wants me to junk it.
桑婭
Sonya...
這不過是她的車罷了  不是她
It was her car; it is not her.
無論如何  你趕快處理
In any case, could you wrap it up.
地檢那邊還等著呢
The D.A.'s waiting to prep me.
能不能取出那盤磁帶  它卡住了
Can you get the tape out? It stuck.
這沒問題
That I can do.
拜
Bye.
檢察官聯系不上馬可
Prosecutor can't get hold of Marco.
我也是
Yeah, me neither.
他必須要現身
We need him to show up.
我已經打了十一次電話了
Well, I've called him 11 times
他還沒打回來  所以...
and he hasn't called me back, so..
我想他了
I miss him.
這是好事
That's good.
是嗎
Is it?
是啊  你為什么不去見他呢
Yeah. Why don't you go see him?
他不會希望我去的
Don't think he'd lik that.
都已經...  已經一個月了
Well, it's been ov... it's been over a month.
大家不再聯系  探望  越來越孤單了
People stop calling, checking in, it gets pretty lonely.
我記得
I remember.
帶些點心去?
Bring pastries?
沒錯
There you go.
伊娃·格拉   見過她嗎
她在那家工廠上班
你認識她嗎
我見過她
我帶了好東西給你
Hi. I brought you these.
是這樣的  周五進行預審聽證
So, um.. the preliminary hearing' Friday.
地方檢察官需要你的證詞
The D.A. needs your testimony.
一直沒有你的消息
Haven't heard from you.
還以為會有一場葬禮
Thought there'd be a funeral.
沒有葬禮
No funeral.
你有沒有...  你最近...
Have you, um.. How have you..
我最近如何?  你想問這個嗎
How have I been? Is that your question?
要么爛醉  要么沉睡
I've been drunk. Or asleep.
好吧  阿爾瑪呢
Right. And Alma?
阿爾瑪走了
Alma is gone.
她去哪里了
Oh, where'd she go?
不知道啊  我說她走了
I don't dnow. She's gone, I said.
你還不明白嗎
我的幾個女兒也走了  格斯也死了
And my daughters are gone and Gus is gone!
正常人都知道這些吧
A normal person would know that!
而且  大家都知道不該打電話給我
A-A-And they would know not to call me,
不該敲我門  不該來我家
not to knock door, not to come to my house!
我是想看看你情況如何
Well, I wanted to check on you.
為什么  我們又不熟
Why? You don't know me.
我們曾是搭檔啊
Well, we... we were partners.
不不不  別誤會了
No, no, no, no, no.. Don't misunderstand things.
你我不過是
You and I are just two people
合作辦案罷了
who worked together on a case.
僅此而已
Huh? Nothing more.
看他們蕩秋千的樣子
好像猴子
我想把這個還你
I wanted to give this back to you.
我偷的
I stole it.
她是說真的嗎
我以為被你那亞洲兄弟拿走了
你是我所見過的最差勁的會計
我是來找新搭檔的
I'm looking for new partner.
我這個人沒有搭檔  只有員工
I don't have partners. I have employees.
我有隧道
And I have a tunnel.
你之前從里面運過一具尸體  沒收你錢
You hauled a corpse through it once... for free.
-那你把賬單給我  -我請了
- Send me the bill. - It's on the house.
-你需要一個我這樣的人  -是嗎
- You need someone like me. - Ah, si?
-為什么  -我是白人  還是美國公民
- Why? - I'm white, I'm a citizen.
在美國沒人注意我  你不行
I blend in over there. You don't.
你想做我在埃爾帕索的合伙人
So you'll be my man in El Paso.
百分之十五分成
For 15%.
你太瘦了  需要吃份牛排了
You're too skinny. You need una steak.
我們找個晚上去吃飯吧
We'll go to dinner one night.
這么說是有的談了
Does that mean we have a deal?
每周五公斤貨  我們見面
Five kilos per week. We meet,
然后我付給你錢
I pay you entonces.
順便還可以了解彼此
We get to know each other.
我沒問題
I can do that.
-我對人一向友好  -知道了
- I'm a nice guy, you know. - Okay.
上次我殺的那個人  我很友好地把他的雞雞
Last man I killed, I was nice enough to cut his dick,
蛋蛋  還有嘴唇割下來送給他妻子了
balls, and lips off and send to his wife.
我不想讓她一個人孤單
Didn't want her to get lonely.
克羅斯警探
Detective Cross.
你還記得我嗎
You remember me?
-斯蒂文·林德  -對
- Steven Linder. - That's right.
-最近好嗎  -還行
- How are you? - Fine.
有什么事嗎
What are you doing here?
我的新娘不見了
Well... my bride is missing.
她在華瑞茲的一家工廠工作
She was working at a factory in Juarez.
有人上次見到她是三天前
Last seen three days ago.
你跟她家人聯系過嗎
Have you talked to her family?
-她沒有家人  -朋友呢
- No family. - Hmm, friends?
她自己一個人生活
She's what you call uh, alone in life.
這不是還有你
Except for you.
我叫她新娘時是口誤了
I misspoke when I called her my bride.
其實我是一廂情愿的
She's, uh, more like my intended.
斯蒂文  你是邊橋案件的嫌疑人
Steven, you were a person of interest in the Bridge case.
我知道
I am aware.
我在你的拖車邊上發現了燒過的女人衣服
I found burned women's clothes up at your trailer.
我怎么知道你有沒有殺這個女孩
How do I know you didn't take this girl?
-我不是這種人  -你是什么人
- That's not who I am. - Who are you?
-我幫助別人  -我記得你說過
- I help people. - I remember you saying that.
幫助那些受到野蠻丈夫或伴侶之類
Women who are being abused by a violent husband,
虐待的女人
partner, or what have you.
她們都是怎么找到你的
How do they find you?
我因為做這種事在圈子里小有名氣
I've become kind of known for this sort of work.
你把人帶到這里來
You bring them here?
我這里有藥品  營養食品
I have medical supplies, nutritious food,
水  在這里休息也很安全
water... safe place to rest.
你可以看看里面
You, you can look inside.
請你退后
Stand back, please.
我燒掉她們的東西是怕別人找到她們
I burn their things so they can't be tracked.
然后她們去哪里
Where do they go next?
一個安全的地方
A safe house.
-你為什么做這個  -因為我有這個能力
- Why do you do it? - 'Cause I can.
這種事非同尋常啊  斯蒂文
That's pretty unusual, Steven.
-對  但不違法吧  -不違法
- Yeah, but not illegal. - No, no.
你為什么將伊娃稱為新娘呢
Why did you call Eva you bride when she wasn't?
因為我認定她了
Because I am bound to her.
她也這么想嗎
Does she feel the same way?
這你得問她
You have to ask her.
她有可能只是回男友那去了嗎
So is there any chance she just went back to her boyfriend?
不太可能
No, not really, nope.
我會一直尋找她  直到找到為止
I'll keep looking for her. Tirelessly, until I find her.
但...  執法部門或許能幫我
But I think... law enforcement would be helpful.
我并不是華瑞茲的警察
I'm not a Juarez cop.
帶走她的車上掛著德州的牌照
Well, the car that picked her up had Texas plates.
你會幫我找到她嗎
Will you help me find her?
陽光照射的感覺真好
Doesn't the sun feel nice?
是啊  要是你想得皮膚癌的話
Yeah, if you're into skin cancer.
這兒空氣真清新  一點也不夸張
Fresh air. It's not overrated.
感覺自己像個80歲的老人一樣
I feel lik I'm 80 years old.
因為你一直像病人一樣生活
Cause you're living like an invalid.
哎呀  真不巧我是個病人
Uh, hello I am an invalid.
但你得自己轉輪椅了
You're ready t wheel yourself.
-什么  -你得學會用這個
- What? - You need to learn how to use this.
這只是暫時的而已
It's only temporary.
那這段時間誰會幫你推呢  反正不是我
Well, who's gonna push you around in the meantime? Not me.
我感覺好差
I feel shitty.
這里氣氛不太好  你還是回來工作吧
It's depression here, you got to come back to work.
你知道我越過大橋時心里在想什么
You know what I was thinking when I was sailing over that bridge?
你問我  我問誰去
Check me out, I' superman.
別讓我死  我想活著
Don't let me die. I want to live.
-你的確活下來了  -但為了什么呢
- And you did. - Yeah, but for what?
生命太短  但我已經浪費了很多時光
Life is short, and I've already wasted so much of mine.
順便說句  你可別學這樣
I don't recommend it by the way.
遵命  尤達宗師
Okay, Yoda.
尤達  《星球大戰》中人物
我親眼看到你摔下來
I saw you fall, Daniel.
丹尼爾  太可怕了
It was scary as shit.
從我的視角看也挺嚇人的
It was pretty scary from my point of view, too.
你還活著我真是太高興了
I'm really gla you're alive.
你愛我  你只想懷我的孩子
You love me. You just want to have my babies.
-病房里見吧  -等等
- See you back there. - Wait, wait, wait, wait.
我看玩笑呢
I was... I was kidding.
別就那樣走了
Hey, don't just walk away.
我只有一只胳膊
I... Hey, I only got one arm.
她在華瑞茲失蹤的
She disappeared in Juarez.
-車掛著美國的車牌  -還掛著
- The car had American plates. - Still?
她在工廠工作
She worked in factory,
很多廠主都住在埃爾帕索
and a lot of those managers live in El Paso.
-那在華瑞茲還需要人手  -我知道
- Well, we're gonna nee somebody in Juarez. - I know.
他跟你說別再打擾他
He told you to leave him be.
他很在意這事
He'd care about this.
而且他也需要回來工作
And he really needs to get back to work.
好吧  祝他好運
Well, then... Well, good luck.
開修理廠的車感覺怎么樣
How're you getting on with the motor pool car?
沒有卡帶錄放機
It doesn't have tape deck.
多謝
Thank you.
卡門一直在問你什么時候能去做客
Carmen keeps asking when you're gonna come on up to the house.
-快了  -我們等著你來
- Soon. - We're gonna hold you to that.
-好夢  -晚安
- Nighty night. - Night.
請往這邊走
沒事  我不想做筆錄了
你在醫院里說他把你鎖起來了
這是很要緊的事
這邊走
在這里
是啊  就在這里
只是待一會兒
別緊張
馬可  我需要你幫忙
Marco. I need your help.
麻煩把這個女人請出去
這個姑娘  伊娃·格拉
There's this girl, Eva Guerra...
她是危險分子  曾開槍打我
她已經失蹤三天了
She's been missing for three days.
一個在華瑞茲失蹤的姑娘
A missing girl in Juarez.
上帝啊  看啊  馬可...
Oh, my God. Look, Marco..
我這兒有個小杯子  我們用它海底撈針吧
I have this little glass here. Let's empty the ocean with it.
我知道你是在意這些失蹤女孩的  我知道
I know you care abou those girls. I know you do.
我要去衛生間了  你可不能跟著我了
Just gonna go to the only place you cannot follow me.
好了  現在該帶你回家了
All right. Taking you home.
來人幫個忙
好了  起來  起來
Come on, get up. Get up
謝謝  行了
Gracias. Okay.
現在走吧
Now...
-你沒有孩子  -是
- You don't have children. - No
所以你沒法理解那種...
So you don't understand, then, that..
是啊  你理解不了
Of course you don't.
你不理解的事太多了
You don't understand a lot of things.
-如果你非開槍不可  -小聲點
- If-if-if you had to shoot me.. - Keep your voice down.
你就該直接殺了我
...you should have killed me!
-什么  -他是我的兒子啊
- What. - He was my kid!
他死了  我也就死了
He goes, I go!
-鄰居都睡覺呢  -他們為什么能睡得著
- People are sleeping. - Why are they sleeping?
因為現在已經凌晨三點了
Because it's 3:00 in the morning.
可我的孩子不在了  永遠不在了
And my son is gone. Forever gone.
我的孩子被殺害  你們怎么能睡得著
-鑰匙呢  -鑰匙...
- Key? - Keys...
-好了  -我能行
- Okay? - I got it.
-謝謝你  桑婭  -沒事
- Sonya, thank you. - All right.
-你該走了  走啊   -不要
- You gotta go, I said go! - No.  I said no.
我要留下
I am staying
你以為你是誰啊
Who do you think you are?
我沒什么朋友  馬可
I don't find people very often, Marco.
那是自然  你怎么可能交到朋友
你不是這么想的
You don't think that.
-無所謂了  -但你是在乎的  馬可
- I don't care . - But... you care, Marco.
我知道你是在乎的
I know you care.
這就是我想說的
That's what I mean.
所以別再說我不是你的搭檔了  好嗎
So don't tell me you're not my partner. Okay?
也不要趕我走
And don't send me away.
因為我沒有別的朋友了
'Cause I don't.. I don't have another one.
-好了  -這里
- All right. - In here.
好了
All right.
-他的氣息還在  -喝點水
- I still can smell him. - Drink this.
抱歉
Sorry.
-格斯有點喜歡你  -我知道
- Gus had a crush on you. - Yeah.
-你知道  -他曾送給我巧克力
- You knew that? - He bought me chocolates.
-我都不知道  -我說  如果我們約會
- I didn't know that. - I told him you wouldn't like that
-你會不高興的  -是啊  我肯定不高興
- if we dated. - Nope, I would not.
他是個好孩子
He was a sweet boy.
是啊
He was.
好了  躺好
Okay. Here we go.
我總是忍不住要想他
Can't stop thinking about him.
-我知道  -我是說戴維
- I know - David, I mean.
為什么他能活下來
Why does he get to live?
早上好
Good morning.
你在這里過夜的嗎
You stayed?
你不記得了嗎
You don't remember?
我母親每次宿醉之后的早上
My mom always liked eggs in the morning
都喜歡吃雞蛋
after a rough night.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你整理床鋪了嗎
Did you make your bed?
你難道是我老媽不成
What are you, my mother?
當我姐姐去世時
When my sister died...
我在漢克和他妻子家住了一陣
I stayed with Hank and his wife for a while.
卡門給我訂了一條規矩
Carmen had one rule for me.
按時起床并整理好床鋪
Always get up and make your bed.
不管我有多難過
No matter how bad I felt.
日子總要過下去的
I had to face the day.
我今天會去警察局一趟  問候大家
I think I'll go into the station today. Say hello.
我能一起去嗎
Can I come?
你想調查那個女孩的資料
You want to run the girl's name?
是的  拜托了
Yes, please.
好吧
Okay.
看吧  我還是記得點什么的
See, I remember some things.
你認得她嗎
她失蹤了嗎
是的
我告訴你哪里可以找到她們
真高興見到你  你還好嗎
馬可  我的朋友
你收到了帕洛瑪做的食物嗎
是的很美味  幫我謝謝她
也謝謝你  西莉亞
應該的
我可以再做一些
什么風把你吹來了
And what brings you here?
我們的合作不是已經結束了嗎
I thought our work is done?
我在找一個最后出現在華瑞茲的失蹤女孩
Looking for a missing girl. Last seen in Juarez.
我想我們可以查一下她的資料
Uh, I said we could run her name.
那當然
Of course.
她的名字是伊娃·格拉   今年23歲
Her name is Eva Guerra, 23 years old.
你回來上班了嗎
暫時還沒有
慢慢來  不著急
真可惜戴維·泰特被美國人收押了
他殺了一個警察的兒子
要在我們這一定得讓他血債血償
以牙還牙
我知道
找到什么了嗎
Anything?
找不到她的記錄
No record of her.
沒有人符合她的描述
No one matches her description.
真抱歉
So sorry.
我們先失陪了
Now, if you'll excuse us.
我真的一口都吃不下了
I honestly cannot eat another bite.
這比醫院的食物美味太多了
So much better than hospital food.
不喝點啤酒嗎
No beer for you?
不用了
Um... no.
要是有背部按摩我倒不介意
A back rub would be great, though.
你那命根子還能用嗎
So does everything still work down there?
-埃琳娜  -怎么了
- Elena! - What?
只是個問題而已
It's just a question.
我的男性雄風沒有問題  謝謝關心
My mighty twig and my berries are fine, thank you.
你可不想嫁給一個坐輪椅的男人
是的我不想
你的余生都要推著他到處走
你需要一個能照顧你的男人
她在說什么  在談論我嗎
Hey, what's she saying? She's talking about me, huh?
她不想艾德里安娜嫁給你
She doesn't think Adriana should marry you.
是啊  你再說一遍試試
Yeah, you can say that again.
我不想結婚  媽媽
別說這種話
我不會結婚的  你是知道的
夠了
什么夠了
注意你的言辭
別在丹妮拉面前說這種話
我不想你教她這些
不  這比保護她強多了
你們沒必要保護我
你把陰道稱為花
陰道
就是它的叫法才讓我擔心
好了  這是一個平靜的家庭之夜
Nice, calm evening at home, huh.
這是一個荒唐的家庭  我已經煩透了
This is the crazy house.I'm so sick of it.
這是你的毛病
我希望你去教堂問問神父
我幫家里負擔費用的時候
可沒聽你抱怨我的毛病
為什么你們要發這么大的火呢
也許我們可以去
Hey, you know, maybe we could go,
吃冰淇淋或是什么的
like, get some ice cream or something
因為我是同性戀
We can't Because I date women.
我是這個家族的恥辱
I'm an embarrassment to the family.
滾出去
非常樂意
糟糕
Oh, shit.
你們這邊的口利左香腸不錯
There's something about the chorizo on your side.
你經常在華瑞茲吃早餐嗎
You start your mornings in Juarez often?
我認為這可能是最好的機會
I figured I had the best chance of you,
向你展示
showing u.....
所以呢
So?
所以我只是想和你談談
So I wanted to talk that's all.
我估計你今天可能不會去法庭
Occurred to me you might not be at court today.
我還沒有決定
I haven't decided yet.
可你起來了  穿戴整齊  剃了胡子
Well, you're up,you're dressed, you're shaved.
那是個好兆頭
That's a good sign.
現在能安下心了嗎
You're able to find any peace?
一天中只有那么十秒鐘
Ten seconds a day.
你不該如此
That ain't right.
當我早晨睜開雙眼的時候
When I open my eyes in the morning...
有那么十秒鐘
For ten seconds,
我不記得他已經死了
I don't remember he's gone.
這就是我現在的生活
That this is my life now.
你希望法律來制裁戴維·泰特嗎
Can you let the system take care of David Tate?
這樣你才能讓自己釋懷
So you can take care of yourself?
我不知道
I don't know.
無論有沒有你指證  他都會進監獄
Well, he's gonna go to prison with or without you testified.
這些都不重要  不是嗎
Then it doesn't matter, does it?
但如果你說出來
But if you say it.
我也會說  桑婭也會說的
And I'm gonna say it Sonya's gonna say it
但如果你說出來
But if you say it...
你可能就會好受點
you just maybe might leave it there a little bit.
也許會  也許不會
Maybe. Maybe not.
像猜謎游戲  是吧
It's all a guessing game, isn't it?
也許你明早上起床時會增加一秒
But just saying that you might get yourself
不難受的時間
another second in the morning.
你現在住哪
埃爾帕索
和誰
你真想知道嗎
你現在怎么不用去上班
我上晚班  相當于升職了
你還想上學嗎
我沒你那么聰明
你沒回答我的問題
新來了個經理
人很好
很可愛
可愛
別擔心  他都快三十了
他很友好  不像其他人
請給我四個牛肉餅
媽媽呢
她說你可以回來
只要你改變
或許可以去教堂讓上帝幫助你
丹妮拉  這個和上帝沒關系
謝謝
Gracias.
你來了
You came.
是啊  我來了
Yeah, I came.
做得對
Good for you.
謝謝
Thank you.
西莉亞
出什么事了
我受不了了
進來說
請坐
我再也不能默不作聲
冷眼旁觀
我受不了了
我明白
但請冷靜下來
你要小心處理你知道的事情
你知道薩帕塔吧
埃米利亞諾·薩帕塔  墨西哥革命領袖  民族英雄
"寧可站著死  也不跪著活"
告訴我  發生什么事了
我看到了一些情況
你看到什么了
你們找的那個女孩  伊娃
我看到她在警察局
什么時候
昨天
一個警察把她帶走了
好吧
OK.
我們得幫助她
交給我吧  好嗎
好吧
Okay.
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯
冰藍
圈圈
No.Zero
屯栗子
翻譯
胖兔純
蓬蓬裙
foolyangyang
Luna心Luge
校對
wdjmhs
時間軸
面條打包子
imok
chance-coco
后期  吉吉
總監  wdjmhs
邊橋謎案
第一季   第十二集